https://www.warmup.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Our mission is to be the most trusted and innovative heating brand in the world.
We value the trust of all our stakeholders; including resellers, homeowners and installers.
So we can offer you the very best service possible, it is necessary for us to collect some personal data from you and your trust in how we handle this data is very important to us.
We acknowledge the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 and have created this privacy policy and privacy notice to both inform you and give you peace of mind in what we do with your personal data, in relation to:
Visiting warmup.com
Purchasing products or services from us
Registering with us for product related information, a service or subscription
Using a SMART Thermostat and our associated smartphone apps.
Our guiding principles & values
We have guiding principles and values, and will always strive to be:
Proud of what we do and what our stakeholders think of us
Positive in our mindset, attitude and the way we interact with all stakeholders
Proactive in delivering what our stakeholders need
Accountable to our stakeholders.
Our principles and values extend to how we manage personal data:
We are committed to protecting your personal data and respecting your privacy
We only collect the personal data needed to offer our products and services to you and as necessary to operate our business
We do not pass your information to other companies for marketing purposes
You can decide how we contact you with offers of products or information which we think you may be interested in.
Further information
We have published a Privacy notice which provides more detail about:
Why we use your personal information
Our legal reasons for using it
Use of cookies on our websites
Protecting your personal data
Your rights in relation to your personal data.
To view our Privacy Notice, please click here.
If you have any questions about personal data, please contact us@warmup.com
Support Dealer Locator Running Cost Calculator Register a warranty2020 PricebookWarmupedia - Online Technical Help
